{"sid": "JPEIACB5RON6_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 626835, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 626835, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["calc_7", 630465], ["calc_+", 631385], ["calc_6", 631841], ["calc_8", 632129], ["calc_+", 632617], ["calc_8", 633057], ["calc_3", 633497], ["calc_=", 633913], ["submit", 641289]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "286", "answered_time": 641289, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "286", "question_time_start": 641289, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 646253]], "time_left_end": "281", "answered_time": 646253, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "281", "question_time_start": 646253, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 660793]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 660793, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 660793, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 665551]], "time_left_end": "262", "answered_time": 665551, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "262", "question_time_start": 665552, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 694959]], "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 694959, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 694959, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 698898]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 698898, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 698898, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 706360]], "time_left_end": "221", "answered_time": 706360, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "221", "question_time_start": 706360, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 710300]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 710300, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 710300, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 715150]], "time_left_end": "212", "answered_time": 715150, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "212", "question_time_start": 715150, "question": "76+87", "correct_answer": 163, "events": [["submit", 732314]], "time_left_end": "195", "answered_time": 732314, "user_answer": "153", "user_correct": "False", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 732314, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "195", "question_time_start": 732314, "question": "4+8+6+59", "correct_answer": 77, "events": [["submit", 741026]], "time_left_end": "186", "answered_time": 741026, "user_answer": "77", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "186", "question_time_start": 741026, "question": "84+459", "correct_answer": 543, "events": [["submit", 764692]], "time_left_end": "163", "answered_time": 764692, "user_answer": "543", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "163", "question_time_start": 764692, "question": "9+77+48", "correct_answer": 134, "events": [["submit", 784008]], "time_left_end": "143", "answered_time": 784008, "user_answer": "134", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "143", "question_time_start": 784008, "question": "79+586", "correct_answer": 665, "events": [["submit", 794776]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 794776, "user_answer": "665", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 794776, "question": "6+97+17", "correct_answer": 120, "events": [["submit", 803214]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 803214, "user_answer": "120", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 803215, "question": "13+97+54+97", "correct_answer": 261, "events": [["submit", 825852]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 825852, "user_answer": "261", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 825852, "question": "9+6+7+93", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 831164]], "time_left_end": "96", "answered_time": 831164, "user_answer": "115", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "96", "question_time_start": 831164, "question": "8+64+99", "correct_answer": 171, "events": [["submit", 839100]], "time_left_end": "88", "answered_time": 839100, "user_answer": "171", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "88", "question_time_start": 839100, "question": "93+73", "correct_answer": 166, "events": [["submit", 845177]], "time_left_end": "82", "answered_time": 845177, "user_answer": "166", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "82", "question_time_start": 845177, "question": "49+79", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 852633]], "time_left_end": "75", "answered_time": 852633, "user_answer": "128", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 852633, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "75", "question_time_start": 852633, "question": "6+24+68", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 858849]], "time_left_end": "68", "answered_time": 858849, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "68", "question_time_start": 858849, "question": "3+38+14", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 863661]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 863661, "user_answer": "55", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 863661, "question": "7+48+93", "correct_answer": 148, "events": [["submit", 883636]], "time_left_end": "44", "answered_time": 883636, "user_answer": "148", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "44", "question_time_start": 883636, "question": "64+78+24+48", "correct_answer": 214, "events": [["submit", 900837]], "time_left_end": "26", "answered_time": 900837, "user_answer": "214", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "26", "question_time_start": 900837, "question": "94+619", "correct_answer": 713, "events": [["submit", 921224]], "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 921224, "user_answer": "713", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 921224, "question": "48+718", "correct_answer": 766, "events": [["submit", 926686]], "time_left_end": "1", "answered_time": 926686, "user_answer": "756", "user_correct": "False", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "1", "question_time_start": 926686, "question": "7+3+8+77", "correct_answer": 95, "events": []}}}}}